[
    {
        "title": "Round 7 Sport and Leisure"
    },
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "Other than The Epee and Foil, what other weapon is used in fencing?",
        "answer": "The Sabre"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "In inches, how wide is the beam in womenâ€™s gymnastics?",
        "answer": "4 inches"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "What colour is the 8 ball in a game of pool?",
        "answer": "Black"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "In which game might you peg out?",
        "answer": "Cribbage"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "The Calcutta Cup is played between which two countries?",
        "answer": "England and Scotland"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "In which UK leisure activity has lightning caused the most fatalities?",
        "answer": "Fishing"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "How many numbers are there on a roulette wheel?",
        "answer": "37"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "How many jumps are there in the grand national?",
        "answer": "30"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "Which city was the first to host the Olympic games twice?",
        "answer": "Paris"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "Who was the first professional footballer to be knighted?",
        "answer": "Sir Stanley Matthews"
    }
]
